Hello! I am Karen Yanagibori, Yuren Sugiura, Hitomi Hasegawa, Suzuki Hayasaki, and
I am Manana Ryuga and Kokka Fujiwara. This time, we are going to sing about the blue sky without covering ourselves with our thoughts.
Each member will sing 2 phrases at a time, and if they can sing until the chorus of the first song, they will be able to sing the chorus happily at the end and be successful.
I see! Let's do our best! What should we do with this group?
What shall we do? Do you think you can do it? I don't know. But I think we can make it after the third time, don't you?
I wonder if we'll be able to get along better than we thought. You think you can do it? One time, one time, one time, one time! It's a one-shot deal!
By the way, I'm one of the members who can sing here, too. Who is good at singing?
Wait a minute!
I think I can sing, I think I have a good sense of pitch, I think I have a good sense of pitch here too!
You have a good sense of pitch.
Bell-like, I have an image that this group likes to sing a lot. They like music.
Yes, they like music.
I know what you mean.
I like your singing voice, Ms. Sugiura.
I'm looking forward to it.
Co-starring! Perform together!
I want to sing a lot if I'm going to deliver a good singing voice to everyone.
Yes!
For sure!
Sure!
I can read your singing voice!
Surely!
Then, the six of us will join forces!
Let's work together!
Oooh!
Well then, let's have the first challenge!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Maybe I'm good!
It's a given!
No mistakes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
What does that mean?
Now, now, now, the first time!
That's the first one!
Five millimeters in four minutes! 5mm in 4 minutes!
Ooh!
Four minutes!
Five minutes!
Where did you put it, by the way?
What's it look like?
Yee-ha ha!
No! No! No!
No! No!
I'm just being an adult that day.
What's up?
What's with the popularity lamps?
That's what everyone said at first.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm getting the hang of it.
I told you we suck at this.
The second challenge is starting.
Oh, no.
I'm scared.
I'm so nervous.
I still remember you from sometime ago
Waving big in the sun.
I waved.
Oh, no!
This is gonna be hard.
What do you want me to do?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm lost.
I'm a little lost.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
He's doing it.
Oh, no.
It's psychological warfare. Psychological warfare.
Fifth start.
Let's go sexy.
Take six.
Hmm.
I thought that might happen, but I went for it, and it didn't work.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to talk.
Come on, let's go.
Kian, you look like him.
I'm sending you the sixth one.
I think you're giving away too much.
Yeah, I think so.
Start the sixth.
You're scaring me.
Thank you for your time.
I still remember you from back in the day.
Waved big in the sunshine
Reflecting on that
I'm sorry I didn't forget you
I don't know what to do
Nice try
I'm sorry
I'll give it to you if you take one step forward.
One step forward.
Let's start the challenge for the seventh time.
I'll never get tired of the seventh one.
I'll never get tired of it.
For the seventh time
The seventh time
For the seventh time.
I've been waiting for you, Narco!
Seven times!
Great Padüs Hot start!
1 day
great aerial shot!
by H.
I still remember you from sometime ago, waving big in the sunshine. I still remember you from sometime ago, waving your hand loudly in the sunlight.
Your short-sleeved shirt, the way it was so white.
I think it's the stubbornness of youth
We always took a break from whatever dreams we had, that's why we loved each other so much.
That we were always able to start running, on-track, weaving Sugar Girl
That day Database help yo
Sitting in the finger shape of change without flipping
fitting Song and evading
ah ah ah ah ah ah
me
We
wanted to be
Where is começar
Where is
Where is Lima?
We're flying to the sky, we're aiming for the sun
Even the sun miracles
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Me.
I'm a soldier, and the sentence is, "I'm a...
Luretor, you and care.
Oh, my God.
me
oa
It was sunny.
Stylus!
I'm so happy.
Here we are.
I had a feeling you'd give it away.
Xujiya, I was wondering if you'd give me something.
I did it in one shot.
It took me an hour and a half, but I'm glad I did it so fast.
Today!
Yes, so think about the blue sky! The song was a great success!
I was so nervous that I couldn't fail, but I'm glad I succeeded!
We were really nervous. If we had failed, it would have been too late.
We were able to communicate. How many times are we going to do this?
I think we'll do it! I think we'll do it eight times! I think we're going to do it! I think he'll do it in eight!
Ellen, on the other hand, will be done in 8!
I wish we could do it again. Finally, I'd like to send a chorus from us to you, the viewers.
But I'd like to sing the phrase from the place where we succeeded earlier, and we'll sing it in turn and join in a big chorus at the end.
I'm still attached to my phrase.
Start the music!
Don't be nervous!
I feel like I'm up all the time.
I don't know what to do.
Jump from me.
Jump.
I still remember you from sometime ago
I waved big in the sun
The difference between that short-sleeved shirt and that mass
I think it's the stubbornness of youth
I felt like I could make any dream come true
That's why you were able to smile so much
Now that I'm older I envy him
That we were always able to run
Wearing the suit we hated that day
Oh!
With my mediocre haircut
And I'm a boring person now.
How did you feel?
Where's the blue sky we wanted to see?
Now we're surrounded by buildings and buildings.
I've lost sight of the sun I was aiming for
You reminded me of something I'd forgotten
You reminded me of who I'd forgotten I was
Thank you very much.